Cannot give up.
Most of you are
happy to be losers
part time. You want
to escape. You
don't want to lose
her anymore. But
then that new video
game comes out.
I'll just play the
video game. I'll
just be a loser for
two more weeks.
Then I'll get back
to trying to escape
the matrix. It
doesn't work that
way because you
jump in and out of
complacency from
I'm happy to be a
loser,
do loser things to
I can't be a loser
anymore. When you
jump in and out,
you never get
momentum. Cannot
quit. You cannot
give up. You need
that momentum to
break free.
And a rocket is
flying out towards
the moon to escape
the atmosphere. It
doesn't *******
pause halfway up
the sky, does it?
No, it keeps going,
or finally in the
right place at the
right time. You are
the only person who
can make this work,
and you're also the
only person who can
**** this up.